[
  {
    "question": "Sarah Howe’s “Relativity” starts in",
    "a": "the stars",
    "b": "the dark",
    "c": "the Sun",
    "d": "a brain",
    "e": "a computer",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The title of “Relativity” refers to a theory first proposed by",
    "a": "Albert Einstein",
    "b": "Galileo Galilei",
    "c": "Marie Curie",
    "d": "Isaac Newton",
    "e": "Stephen Hawking",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What poetic form is Sarah Howe’s “Relativity”?",
    "a": "sonnet",
    "b": "free verse",
    "c": "villanelle",
    "d": "elegy",
    "e": "ballad",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stephen Hawking’s artificial voice was originally created for a(n)",
    "a": "answering machine",
    "b": "artificial intelligence",
    "c": "public transportation announcement",
    "d": "telephone directory",
    "e": "audiobook",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "The format of “Relativity” resembles",
    "a": "train tracks",
    "b": "a constellation",
    "c": "ocean waves",
    "d": "a wheel",
    "e": "winding footpaths",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which particles does Howe mention in “Relativity”?",
    "a": "protons",
    "b": "bosons",
    "c": "electrons",
    "d": "photons",
    "e": "neutrons",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scientific principle does Howe mention in “Relativity”?",
    "a": "Newton’s third law",
    "b": "Kepler’s law of orbit",
    "c": "second law of thermodynamics",
    "d": "Hawthorne effect",
    "e": "the Doppler effect",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In “Relativity”, Howe uses a simile to compare light to",
    "a": "horses",
    "b": "dogs",
    "c": "cars",
    "d": "rivers",
    "e": "balls",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following contradictions does Howe NOT depict in “Relativity”?",
    "a": "past and present",
    "b": "art and science",
    "c": "light and dark",
    "d": "personal and universal",
    "e": "small and large",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Howe personifies light in “Relativity” by saying that it",
    "a": "feels excited",
    "b": "screams out loud",
    "c": "opens its eyes",
    "d": "smiles and laughs",
    "e": "waves goodbye",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was Sarah Howe born?",
    "a": "London",
    "b": "Cambridge",
    "c": "Hong Kong",
    "d": "Singapore",
    "e": "Tokyo",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which institution did NOT award Sarah Howe a fellowship?",
    "a": "Radcliffe Institute",
    "b": "Gonville and Caius College",
    "c": "University College London",
    "d": "Civitella Ranieri Foundation",
    "e": "King’s College London",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Howe’s A Certain Chinese Encyclopedia was a(n)",
    "a": "novella",
    "b": "article",
    "c": "pamphlet",
    "d": "children’s book",
    "e": "zine",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sarah Howe describes the form of “Relativity” similar to a",
    "a": "meteor",
    "b": "comet",
    "c": "nebula",
    "d": "black hole",
    "e": "star",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "For which award did Howe’s Loop of Jade not receive a nomination or win?",
    "a": "T.S. Eliot Prize",
    "b": "Young Writer of the Year Award",
    "c": "Forward Prize",
    "d": "Eric Gregory Award",
    "e": "Seamus Heaney Centre Poetry Prize",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  }
]

